A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (L-Z), Accession 2021:051 FA1790
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Other, 2002-2017; 6
  - Emergency/Impact Fund, 2009-2017; 2
    - Miami Dade College Foundation Inc. - Hurricane Maria Relief Efforts (2017-55095) (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - Miami Dade College Foundation Inc. - Innovation Grant Fund, Dr. Eduardo Padron (2016-53630), 2016-2017 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Miami Foundation - Puerto Rico Relief and Recovery Fund: Walmart Match (2017-55085) (Box 13, Folder 174)
      Hurricane Maria
    - Miami Foundation - Virgin Islands Relief Fund (2017-55086) (Box 13, Folder 175)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - 21st Century Membership Experience (2016-53478) (Box 27, Folder 332)
    - National Multiple Sclerosis Society, South Florida Chapter - MS Gala Luncheon (2016-53638) (Box 29, Folder 359)
    - New World Foundation - Diverse Asset Managers Initiative (2017-54906) (Box 32, Folder 399)
    - New York Public Library, Astor, Lenox, and Tilden Foundations - James Baldwin Archive Acquisition (2016-53594), 2014-2016 (Box 32, Folder 404)
    - New York Public Radio - Susan Crawford Charitable Recommendation (2015 MLS Speaker) (2015-50617) (Box 32, Folder 407)
    - New Venture Fund - Media Democracy Fund: Net Neutrality (2017-54686) (Box 33, Folder 418)
    - Ohio State University Foundation - The Future of Libraries in the Digital Age (2016-52263) (Box 36, Folder 448)
    - Philanthropy for Active Civic Engagement (PACE) - General Operating Support (2013-47869) (Box 38, Folder 484)
    - Philanthropy Northwest - Mission Investors Exchange (2013-47200) (Box 43, Folder 540)
    - Philanthropy Roundtable - Website Renovation (2017-54685) (Box 43, Folder 543)
    - Philanthropy Roundtable - 25th Anniversary Matching Gift Campaign (2016-53296) (Box 43, Folder 545)
    - Philanthropy Roundtable - First Amendment Programming, 2016 Annual Meeting (2016-53555) (Box 43, Folder 546)
    - Puerto Rico Community Foundation - Hurricane Maria Relief Efforts (2017-55096) (Box 47, Folder 607)
    - St. Thomas University - Hurricane Maria Relief Efforts (2017-55084) (Box 51, Folder 661)
    - The Salvation Army, Columbia - Hurricane Joaquin (2015-51695) (Box 52, Folder 663)
    - South Florida Progress Foundation - Library Funding Survey (2014-49242) (Box 58, Folder 754)
    - South Florida Progress Foundation - General Operating Support (2009-0024) (Box 58, Folder 755)
    - University of Akron Foundation - Support for President Wilson (2016-53569), 2016-2017 (Box 69, Folder 913)
    - University of Maryland - Honoring Brit Kirwan's Service to the Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics (KCIA) (2016-53365) (Box 71, Folder 928)
    - Washington State University Foundation - Dr. Elson S. Floyd Medical Education Founders Fund (2015-51102) (Box 79, Folder 1018)
    - Welcoming Center for New Pennsylvanians - Civic Engagement Leadership Lab (2017-54093) (Box 79, Folder 1024)
    - Zoological Society of Philadelphia - Andrew Swinney Fund (2016-52580) (Box 82, Folder 1069)
  - Communications, 2013-2015; 3
    - Lyndon Baines Johnson Foundation - Vietnam War Summit (2016-52431), 2013-2015 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Membership, 2002-2017; 4
    - Miami-Dade Broadband Coalition - 2017 Membership (2016-53651) (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Miami-Dade Broadband Coalition - South Florida Digital Alliance (2015-51957) (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Miami-Dade Broadband Coalition - South Florida Digital Alliance (2014-49788), 2013-2014 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Miami Foundation - Prototype Fees and Fiscal Agency Fees (2017-53796) (Box 12, Folder 162)
    - Miami Foundation - Fiscal Agency Fees (2016-52630), 2013-2016 (Box 13, Folder 181)
    - Miami Foundation - Fiscal Agency Fees (2014-48831) (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Minnesota Council on Foundations - 2017 Membership (2017-54015) (Box 24, Folder 289)
    - Minnesota Council on Foundations - 2015 and 2016 Membership (2016-52069) (Box 24, Folder 290)
    - Minnesota Council on Foundations - 2014 Membership (2014-48918) (Box 24, Folder 291)
    - North Carolina Network of Grantmakers - 2017 Membership (2017-54114) (Box 34, Folder 428)
    - North Carolina Network of Grantmakers - 2016 Membership (2016-52122) (Box 34, Folder 430)
    - North Carolina Grantmakers - 2017 Membership (2017-54609) (Box 34, Folder 436)
    - Northern California Grantmakers - 2016 Membership (2016-52075) (Box 35, Folder 437)
    - Philadelphia Network, Greater Philadelphia - 2016 Membership (2016-52066) (Box 43, Folder 538)
    - Philadelphia Network, Greater Philadelphia - 2014 Membership Dues (2014-48256) (Box 43, Folder 539)
    - Philanthropy Ohio - 2016 Membership (2017-54127) (Box 43, Folder 541)
    - Philanthropy Ohio - 2016 Membership (2016-52244) (Box 43, Folder 542)
    - Philanthropy Roundtable - 2016 Membership (2016-52269) (Box 43, Folder 544)
    - Philanthropy Roundtable - 2017 Membership (2016-53587) (Box 43, Folder 547)
    - Southeastern Council of Foundations - 2016 Membership (2016-52111) (Box 57, Folder 741)
    - Southeastern Council of Foundations - 2016 Conference Support (2016-52879) (Box 57, Folder 744)
    - Southeastern Council of Foundations - 2014 Membership (2014-49188) (Box 57, Folder 745)
    - Southeastern Council of Foundations - General Operating Support (2004-0079), 2002-2004 (Box 57, Folder 746)
    - South Florida Progress Foundation - 2016 Greater Miami Chamber Dues (2016-52123) (Box 58, Folder 749)
    - South Florida Progress Foundation - 2017 Greater Miami Chamber Dues (2016-53699) (Box 58, Folder 750)
    - South Florida Progress Foundation - 2015 Greater Miami Chamber Dues (2015-50885) (Box 58, Folder 751)
    - South Florida Progress Foundation - 2015 Alvah H. Chapman Luncheon Support (2015-51603) (Box 58, Folder 752)
      Sponsoring the distribution of Rosabeth Moss Kanther's book, MOVE.
    - South Florida Progress Foundation - 2014 Membership Dues (2014-48823) (Box 58, Folder 753)
    - Southeastern Council of Foundations - 2017 Membership (2017-54016) (Box 58, Folder 758)
    - Technology Affinity Group - 2017 Conference Support (2017-54330) (Box 63, Folder 825)
    - Technology Affinity Group - 2016 Conference Support (2016-52441) (Box 63, Folder 826)
    - Technology Affinity Group - 2017 Membership (2016-53622) (Box 63, Folder 827)
    - Technology Affinity Group - 2015 Conference, Los Angeles (2015-50948) (Box 63, Folder 828)
    - Technology Affinity Group - 2014 Membership (2014-48193) (Box 63, Folder 829)
    - Technology Affinity Group - 2016 Membership (2016-52086) (Box 63, Folder 835)